

# Rúben Sousa

I am a Gameplay Programmer and Front end Developer proficient in C#, HTML, CSS and Arduino.

I have experience with Unreal Engine and Unity, creating engaging gameplay experiences.

Used to working with indie teams with time management and tight deadlines.

#### Contact



+351 914 972 356





https://rubensousa-dev.github.io/



Portugal

#### Soft Skills

**Teamwork** 

Communication

Adaptability

## **Hard Skills**

**Unreal Engine** 

Unity

C# and C++

HTML/CSS/JS

#### **Skills & Abilities**

- · Profecient using C# and OOP languages.
- Comfortable working independently and in team setting.
- Good communication skills.
- 2+ Years of experience working with video games.

#### Experience

## Gameplay Programmer | Butter Games Studios | February 2021 - August 2022

Responsible for all programming and in-engine tasks for all the games developed.

Developed two full project in Unity and Unreal

## Content Manager | AutoMCaldas / StarMotor | January 2018 - August 2020

Worked as a freelancer, performing the role of automotive photographer. I also did image editing, website and ad maintenance.

Finally, I did some work as a graphic designer.

## Front-End Developer & Web Designer | BITCLIQ | February 2020 - June 2020

Developed projects in the areas of Web Design, Front End Development and some work in the area of Graphic Design such as the creation of icons, flayer and mupis.

### Education

Bachelor's Degree In Games and Multimedia - Instituto Politécnico de Leiria - Leiria Portugal (2020 - 2023)

**Tesp Design for Digital Media** - ESAD Instituto Politécnico de Leiria - Leiria Portugal (2018 - 2020)

## Other Accomplishments

- 2022 PlayStation® Talens Award Finalist.
- More than 10 articles written for the video games I have developed.
- Featured on Itch.io's and Indie DB's front page.
- Ambassador of the Voodoo Academy program.
- Best school project developed in Arduino consisting in a vending machine adapted for people with visual impairment.